FROM ME TO YOU
Anyhow, she really is an admirable girl.
The type that makes
you want to root for her.
Really? She must be a
real beauty then too, eh?
I'd say so. In fact she
looks just like that over there.
Hey, c'mon that's givin' me
some major heebie jeebies.
- It's her looks.
- Just her looks, huh?
Sawako.
Heh? Sadako?
Her name! It's her name! It's pronounced
Sawako and written as "cheerful child."
For some reason,
everyone is always afraid of me.
I hear she has a strong sixth
sense, so she draws spirits over to her.
Even her name's
Sadako, like from The Ring.
But all I want is to get along with them.
Her parents must've had foresight to give
her such a perfect name. Know what I mean?
I'm done. Go ahead.
Hey there, Kuronuma.
- Kazehaya, you do your homework?
- Kazehaya is the complete opposite of me.
No, I haven't.
- Right? We're in the same boat.
- It's like everyone gathers around
Kazehaya and everything just flows from
there.
The day of the high
school entrance ceremony...
U- Um...
If you happen to be looking for
Kitahoro High, it's that way.
Thanks alot!
People usually apologize to me when I
talk to them, but he smiled and told me,
"Thank you."
And one day, I'd sincerely hope
I can become a person like him.
She's got this!
- Yes~ good! Keep going!
- The most popular one in class, eh?
Well Kazehaya at least. Sawako on
the other hand is a complete outcast.
Uh... Sadako?
You know Yuka who sat in Sadako's seat?
She was out sick with a cold for a whole
week.
You got this.
- Um... Excuse me...
- Hm?
Hm?
Don't worry, it isn't dirty.
A- And nothing bad
will happen in that seat.
I don't have any powers like that.
I said it!
I really said it.
A seating change, huh?
I hope this time I can get along better
with the people sitting next to me. -Wow,
just like that
Kazehaya's surrounded. -N-No!
It's a little lonely not being able to
share joy over sitting by your friend, or
disappointment over
being seated far away.
Whoever's 19, trade me.
Huh?
Oh... what?
Kazehaya?
Alright, next to Kuronuma.
- I don't want this.
- What?
Yoshida, you're next.
Nope, I'm good right
here. Get outta here Ryu!
No thanks.
Tsk!
My seat... makes me so happy...
I... don't have words...
I'm happy.
Ever since that day, I've had all
these feelings I never knew of before.
My heart's overflowing.
I want to treasure them.
Like I've been given a
gift for the very first time.
- Honestly--
- Hm?
Huh? How goes it, boys?
- And how come you're always like this?
- I just wanted to attend your little
lecture here on how great Sawako is!
Sawako was... just starting to
find her place among her peers.
Yeah, but that was
unfortunately short-lived.
I'm asking you where
this bull crap started!
Sa... Sadako.
- Huh?
That's what I heard.
Sadako's trying to make herself popular
and she's using you, Yano and especially
- Kazehaya in order to do it.
- But I'm happy for you.
You were able to make friends. I
believe their names are Yano and Yoshida?
- Huh?
- Th- They're not my friends!
Those dark rumors about Yano and
Yoshida are pretty extreme huh?
Dark rumors? About being my backup?
That's why they looked so upset
earlier. They must've been hurting.
- It's all Sadako's fault.
- Uh-huh. Because she's always
- hanging around and latching on to them.
- Poor Kazehaya too.
If Sadako continues to hang around him
like this, she'll definitely ruin his
- reputation.
- This is... my fault?
As long as I'm around, I'm sure
I'll only end up hurting them again.
And they don't deserve that.
Things may straighten out eventually... But
Yano and Yoshida are hurting right now,
and I have no idea how I'm supposed
to comfort either of them until then.
That's why, I think it's better to go
back to the way I was and distance myself.
It's for the best I'm sure of it.
She may not look it, but Sawako's
got quite the positive mindset.
Misunderstandings. Rumors.
Ugh, this is beyond frustrating!
Thaaat's right! But now who do
you think is even more frustrated?
If you don't hate me, then why avoid me?
"Don't... talk to me, ever again"
Wait! I'm sorry, I take it back!
I see. So the rumors made it
awkward between you, Yano and Yoshida.
- What if things were the other way around?
- Huh? Like if the rumor was that by
hanging out with you Yano, Yoshida and I
would ruin your reputation...
So we'd distance ourselves from you.
I'd hate that.
I'd want to stay together.
Then Yano and Yoshida
would say the same thing.
It just depends on how
the other person feels.
His kind words... and that smile...
they always push me to keep going.
Hnag in there Kuronuma, you've got this.
Good luck.
- Cool! And handsome to boot!
- Heh?
Heh?
Hey, you! Don't butt into
our conversation like that!
My apologies, I can't
help it! Romance is my thing.
He's too young for this...
such a disappointment!
Squeaky, squeaky, squeaky clean!
So Kazehaya was watching over
Sawako then... The entire time, huh?
Yeah, that's right, and it gave her the
courage she needed. Now, it's her turn to
- stand up for herself and fight.
- You're wrong!
You don't have to leave me alone!
- Just take back what you said.
- What are you talking a--
All of it... Everything that you're saying
is wrong! You don't get it and how could
you?
I guess it's cause you
don't know anything about them.
They've always treated me kindly even
though they never had a reason to. You all
have no idea how much I like both Yano
and Yoshida... more than I can put into
words
...Much more.
That's why...
Y- Yoshida! -She spread those rumors
about you, and you're still gonna help
her?! -It wasn't Sadako.
- She'd never do something like that.
If we say it wasn't her, then it wasn't
and that's that. Get out of here, before I
have to force you out!
So I, would like to ask if
maybe you two would be my...
I would like it if we
could become friends!
You're so silly.
Didn't you know? It's hard for us to do
anything but think the whole world of you.
And besides...
You're worried about friends but you
don't realize you already have them.
Sadako! You, me and Yano? We ARE friends.
We are?
We already... are friends?
Wow... my very first... real friends.
Do you think she's gonna be okay?
Yuka's had a serious crush on Kazehaya
since middle school.
Hey!
- Wait!
- Yuka!
Such stupid girls. I don't know what they
expected... When you make a big scene like
that, of course
Kazehaya's gonna hate you.
- Hey Kurumi!
- Oh.
I've been hearing a lot of rumors
involving Sadako everwhere lately.
Oh yeah, didn't we see her
hanging out with Kazehaya before?
Oh yea, I remember that. We were both
saying stuff like, "Oh my gosh, are the
- two of them dating now?"
- There's no way that would ever happen!
You think so?
If Kazehaya did actually like
her would it be that weird?
Huh? I ddin't know you were
on the Field Day Committee?
Oh. You're here to Kurumi That's great.
You know the album released before the
one I lent you? The cover of that fourth
song... Kazehaya? Are you listening,
- Oh. My bad, what were you talking about?
- The CD that was released
before the one I lent you.
Oh, got it I'll be sure
to bring it next time.
So this time she's the problem, eh...
She was glaring right at Sawako,
I have a bad feeling about it.
Sawako!
Sawako, hi!
And so, if the ball gets passed
here, Sawako, you need to make your move...
Sawako!
- Hm?
See ya!
Bye-bye.
Another one I can't believe
I made another new friend.
To be honest, I didn't exactly work
for it, so it hasn't really sunk in.
Yea we're friends... I mean
it is obvious, isn't it?
I'm new to this but I wonder if making
new friends is supposed to feel like this?
I haven't had much time to process
it, but I know it makes me happy.
- She's so sweet!
I can't take it!
You buncha old fogeys... you're
clearly blind to how that girl is feeling.
Where's this comin' from?
She has a special someone. And it's
one she's been watching over since the
beginning.
To tell you the truth,
there's someone that I like.
Huh?
It's just that I'd like
you to help me out, Sawako.
The person I like... it's Kazehaya.
Kazehaya is going to
have thar special someone?
And I'm going to help with that?
Thank you so much, Sawako.
Really, that makes me so happy!
I can't help you.
Huh?
I don't think it's possible.
It's just I I can't support
you from the bottom of my heart.
So that's why I can't help you.
If I'm honest with myself, well,
I also think of him as special.
- So why do you think he's special?
- U-Umm...
Because he treated you nicely?
- Because he gave you attention? -Uh...
Because he showed you a
little bit of kindness?
I- I guess?
That's just him doing charity work!
You're just looking for someone who treats
you like a normal human being, it
doesn't have to be Kazehaya, right?!
H-hold on! Wait!
Ah, so that was what she wanted.
But if Sawako can refuse her
request, it'll prove she's really grown
- up!
- So she only started seeing Kazehaya in a
different light after speaking with her
- I see...
Like.
Like!
This is what "liking" someone is, right?
Everything I feel towards the person in
front of me. All of it is that kind of
love, isn't it?
The first person I tell should be her.
Somewhere along the line we became
close enough to talk about love.
The one who spread those rumors from
the bathroom incident was... Kurumi.
Sawako... the person responsible
for all that pain you went through
It was all her.
I thought we were...
Despite what I said I've
never considered us friends.
Shouldn't you follow them
so you can all snitch on me?
Once you do, you'll have all
of Kazehaya's sympathy again.
The game's over, huh?
So, in the end it was Sawako's win...
Hey.
I wonder... was that... really enough for her?
Hold on. What are-?
Well wasn't there
something... she still wanted to say?
I wanted to tell you I like Kazehaya.
My feelings for him keep growing, so...
I guess I should say I love him.
Actually, that was what I came
to tell you in the first place.
It's something I been really
wanting to share with you.
I told you you're in my way! I'll never
forgive you for daring to be around
Kazehaya without earning it!
I had assumed with you,
I'd have no trouble winning.
Because nothing you do could ever
compare 'Cause I've always liked Kazehaya.
And I'm sure of that.
I hope this doesn't sound weird or
anything but compared to the first time I
met you, you seem much cuter
now than you were back then.
I know I'm cute, that's not the point!
But but what good is being cute?
It just hurts...
Because I know he doesn't feel the same
way about me as I do about him. Since I've
always watched over him, I can tell.
There's already someone I like.
It's impossible for me to
see anyone else but her.
I'm sorry.
Kazehaya, does me telling you that I
like you make you feel happy at all?
Yeah. Thank you.
They both ended up falling in
love with the exact same person!
So in other words, that makes those two...
... Even if you somehow manage to beat the
million to one odds against you getting
with Kazehaya, I will never, ever be able
to say I'm happy for you! 'Kay?! 'Cause if
he likes a girl, I
automatically hate her guts!
Does that mean we can never be friends?
What do you mean friends?
Uh...
I think you mean rivals.
Woohoo!
I'm gonna have fun tonight! Oh! Isn't
that... Let's take this holy sake and...
A moment of happiness.
A place to make memories
Next time: "Day Off"